<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Jonker Malacca</string>
    <string name="title_food">Delicacies</string>
    <string name="title_food_chinese">Culinary Speciality</string>
    <string name="title_food_nyonya">Nyonya Cuisine</string>
    <string name="title_spot">Cultural Exploration</string>
    <string name="title_spot_tradition">Conventional Business</string>
    <string name="title_spot_wall">Street Art</string>
    <string name="title_spot_association">Provincial Guild Hall</string>
    <string name="title_spot_temple">Place of Worship</string>
    <string name="title_other">Others</string>
    <string name="title_about">About</string>
    <string name="title_about_orign">Genesis</string>

    <string name="about_item_website">Website: </string>
    <string name="about_item_email">Email: </string>
    <string name="unknown_distance">Unknown Distance</string>

    <string name="list_item_address">Address: </string>
    <string name="list_item_business_hour">Business Hour: </string>
    <string name="map_hotspot">Cultural Exploration</string>
    <string name="map_food">Delicacies</string>
    <string name="map_all">All</string>

    <string name="about_ntust_name">National Taiwan University of Science and Technology</string>
    <string name="about_ntust_website">http://www.ntust.edu.tw/</string>
    <string name="about_ntust_description">National Taiwan University of Science and Technology which was founded in 1974 is one of the Taiwan’s leading universities, possessing an excellent record as an outstanding research and educational institution in Asia. An extensive spectrum of programs is offered in an innovative and friendly learning environment.</string>
    <string name="about_pfms_name">Malacca Pay Fong Middle School</string>
    <string name="about_pfms_website">http://www.payfong.edu.my/</string>
    <string name="about_pfms_description">Pay Fong Middle School which was established in 1913 is the only Chinese Independent School in Malacca. It is a non-profit school and thus the school is supported by particularly the Chinese community for the cause of humanitarian education, culture and traditions.</string>
    <string name="about_whc_name">Malacca World Heritage Office</string>
    <string name="about_whc_website"></string>
    <string name="about_whc_description">Malacca World Heritage Office was established in Desember 2011 to plan, conserve and preserve the status of world heritage in Malacca.</string>



    <string name="description_food_chinese">Basically mouth-watering food garnished with the combination of cultural elements should always stimulate your voracious appetite for locally prepared cuisines. When you are here in Malacca, don’t forget to drop by these shops to relish the local delicacies dedicated to you.</string>
    <string name="description_food_nyonya">Baba Nyonya is the term used for the descendants of the 15th through 17th-century Chinese immigrants to Nanyang. The Chinese then married the local females and their distinct background, cultures and customs blended together harmoniously and became Baba Nyonya in “Peranakan” culture.  The male is known as Baba and the female as Nyonya. This is a very unique culture in Melaka where the Chinese culture is assimilated into Malay customs.\n\nNyonya food is made up of pungent and strong-flavored spices from Malay and Chinese style in food preparing. Thus, never miss the chance to taste the fusion cuisine while travelling in Malacca.</string>
    <string name="description_spot_tradition">Despite the dynamic transformation of variant professions, some of the conventional businesses along Malacca River are still fragmentarily retained. Conventional businesses should be explored and supported as there are precious wisdoms and resourcefulness from our ancestors embedded in the unnoticeable products.</string>
    <string name="description_spot_wall">The street art in Malacca is presented in various forms, illustrating the story or history of Malacca. From the mural artwork or graffiti along Malacca River, there are more living stories to be discovered.</string>
    <string name="description_spot_association">Nanyang region, an exclusive term used by Chinese migrants to Southeast Asia. Upon their arrival in this alien environment, an enormous amount of associations were founded in order to take care of the migrants from similar clan or close geographical affinity.</string>
    <string name="description_spot_temple">People pray and worship as they would like to live harmoniously with the people who are different from them. Even though we are adopting different ways in worshipping, we are pursuing the same goal of getting the world a better and more peaceful place to live. Harmony Street is a paradigm for us to copy because temples and mosque of the three main religions of Malaysia are located peacefully along the same street.</string>
    <string name="description_about">Jonker Walk is flanked by heritage houses dating back to the 17th century. The hundred-year buildings, temples and guild halls along the street reflect vividly the image of how the early Chinese migrants strived persistently on the new homeland.\n\nJonker Malacca is a mobile app initiated by Pay Fong Middle School, and created and developed by National Taiwan University of Science and Technology for Malacca World Heritage Office as an alternative tool to introduce the cultural and historical values of Malacca to tourists from all over the world.</string>
</resources>
